Behnaz Shojaei

0452 282 055 | behnaz.shojaei88@gmail.com | Attadale, WA 6156

Data Analyst

Technically strong, with high attention to detail, experience analysing data from a variety of sources providing detailed research and reporting. Strong communication, and previous experience working with and contributing to a high performing team, in a customer driven environment, as a Biomedical Engineer.

- Develops and maintains interactive dashboards and reports using Power BI and Tableau.
- Performs ETL (export, transform and load) processes from different resources.
- Experience with SQL for database management, maintaining data integrity and accessibility, writing query to manipulate and extract data.
- Automates repetitive data processing tasks using Python.

Key Skills and Experience

Coding languages - C++, C#, and Python.

Software - MYSQL, SAP, MEX, Jupyter Notebook, MATLAB, PowerBI, Tableau, VSCode, Microsoft Office.

Data Entry | Recording and Reporting | Data Analysis | Trouble Shooting | Data Manipulation | Data Visualisation | Electronics Design and Simulation | Finite Element Analysis | Research

- Strong IT skills and interest with a working knowledge of a variety of databases and in-house systems, and the capability and willingness to learn new packages.
- Sound analytical and conceptual skills, strong critical thinking and reasoning, experience trouble shooting, anticipating, and analysing issues, developing logical conclusions, testing and assessing complex and detailed equipment and data.
- Administratively strong, with efficient data entry skills, extensive record keeping experience, building reports, and presenting timely and meaningful data to Management.
- Extensive research experience, strong understanding of medical terminology, qualitative data and analysis, communicating findings, using judgement and real-world insights.

Qualifications

Assessed as a professional Biomedical Engineer by Engineers Australia, 2015

Master of Science in Nanoelectronics and Nanotechnology, University of Southampton, UK, 2012.

Bachelor of Science in Biomedical Engineering, University of Esfahan, Iran, 2010.

Employment History

Full-time Parent and Professional Development

Apr 2017 - Present

Primary caregiver for my daughter while focusing on professional growth in data analysis. Undertook training courses to enhance analytical skills, including:

- Python for Data Science Pierian Training
- Power BI Essentials Gini von Courter, LinkedIn Learning
- Data Analytics Robin Hunt, LinkedIn Learning
- Probability and Statistics Luis Serrano, Coursera

Attended workshops and events by WA Data Science Innovation Hub and Insight.

Biomedical Field Engineer, Hollywood Hospital, WA

Jul 2016 - Apr 2017

Reporting to the Site coordinator, working onsite within a team of four, performed detailed preventative maintenance, repairs and testing on a range of biomedical devices including infusion pumps, patient monitoring systems, vital signs monitors, ventilators, and theatre rooms.

- Using both MEX and SAP, working to Australian standards and established safety and quality requirements, completed all required testing and associated reporting, correctly tagging and labelling the device.
- Acknowledged for contribution to annual audit, due to strong organisation and compliance, updated 5000+ reports in the system, over a three-month period, entering qualitative and quantitative data and archiving the reports, meeting all compliance and quality standards.
- Managed on site breakdowns, engaging with appropriate third parties, completing all testing, data entry, reporting and archiving of the file.
- Worked effectively to Australian standards AS/NZS 3200, AS 3003, AS3551, and all established safety and quality requirements.

Biomedical Field Engineer, Behboudsazan Group, Iran. The Behboudsazan Group manufactures patient monitoring systems. Dec 2012 - Mar 2016

Reporting to the Engineering Manager, working in a team of five, providing technical expertise and testing to a range of clients in private or public hospitals, day surgery clinics, doctors and surgeon offices.

 Attended final sales meetings providing technical presentations to clients, addressing concerns and questions, prior to their purchase of a new system.

- Evaluated the site and prepared technical reports on the individual client service and product requirements, ensuring all safety, quality and audit requirements were met.
- Liaised closely with customers, field specialists, and territory managers providing monthly onsite technical assistance. Led the 5-day surgery clinics, providing ongoing preventative maintenance and corrective testing.
- Managed all associated documentation, technical specifications records and reports associated with both new products and maintenance requirements.

Lecturer, Azad University of Najafabad, Iran

Dec 2012 - Jul 2015

- Developed detailed reports and charts using Excel, building reports and presenting data to management, outlining and reporting on student data.
- Lectured and tutored in 'Research Methods in English' and 'Basic Principles and Devices for Rehabilitation' with an average of 240 students per lecture. Developed assessments, workshops and site visits to enhance learning and research opportunities.
- Utilised own web page within the university domain, to provide students with links to additional research papers, designed small online quizzes, providing students with the opportunity to use research methods outlined in the lecture.

References available upon request